Um, I want to pray. So whoever you pray to, whoever you pray to, pray to them.
Thank you, Jordi. Whoever you pray to, pray to them. And I just want us, I want us to speak into
a vibration together. To whom is listening? May we
receive your strength in strengthening each other instead of breaking each other down.
May the forces within us that are spoken to by shadows and darkness, may they be quieted.
May they be quieted by love. May they be quieted by joy. May they be quieted by a desire
to amplify all that is good. We come from the earth. We go back to the earth. We are of the
earth and we have lost our connection. We are in a world that is so processed. It is
so processed with so much manufactured synthetics that we now even manufacture hate. We find
a way to conjure it up for those that we don't know based on things that we don't even believe
in. We are watching an entire people across this world. We're watching entire peoples be
demolished their existence because that connectivity has been disrupted. Let us every day challenge
ourselves to lean in to the part of ourselves that we are constantly being taught to lean out of.
Let us explore avenues that we have been told were closed off to us that are leading us to back to
community, forward to community. And let us really try our best to maybe not even remember, but to
realize what a better future could be if we really challenged ourselves to be different than the trauma
that shaped us. Let us shape ourselves in the image that we hope we are happy to be. In your name we pray. Amen.
Amen. I know that I'm growing because I don't even have hatred for these people that are coming for me.
I have pity for them and I have compassion for them.
Hey Tony, my ex's mama is on here. That's how I'm loved. I have love for them. I know I said come see me in
that caption because I was, that was my darker self talking because we all have a shadow person. We all
have shadows in us, but I hope these people that are taking their time to, to bring me harm.
Um, um, I hope, I hope that you wonder, well, well, one, I hope you understand that that is a reflection
of your own hurt. That's a reflection of your own hurt. And I hope that there is a bomb.
I hope, I hope you find a bomb, B-A-L-M, to soothe that. Because the bomb that I have found
to soothe this is one that's for it's, it's in me, it's fortified in me. And I am, I am so loved
first and foremost by myself. And it took me so long to know that I was worthy of that.
It took me so long. It took me so long to know that I was worthy of loving myself,
but I really do. I really do love myself. And I just, I wish that for everybody because when you
love yourself, you don't harm, you don't harm that way. It ain't even in your functionality.
And I know that there's been people in the past who may feel some type of way about me,
but it's true. I had to learn how to love myself. So I hope that they learn that too. I hope these
people that are, that are using their skill and their talent to, to wield such darkness.
I hope that they understand that as artists, that is such a misuse of your godlike skill. It
really is. It really is. You know, the, you know, the godliness that comes from making something out
of nothing. It's beautiful to be able to do that. So to do that, to, to inflict upon someone else is
trippy. It's really, it's really, it's really irresponsible, but I will continue to love and
I will continue to lead. I'm about to go back on tour. So I'll be back in these streets. And, um,
and I hope, I hope that I continue to show y'all that I am always trying to do my best
and, um, and always trying to pour into like where we are. But I know that I am, I am a supernatural
being and I know this. What someone may call hubris is really just me knowing that I come from
something great and I'm so lucky. I'm so lucky to know that. And I feel like if we all knew that we
would do so much better because we would know, we would know that we have to do better because we
come from something great. We are made of the cosmos. We are made of the soil. Look at how crazy
it is when you see, you know, the galaxies, you like, wow, that's bonkers. Look at how crazy it is
when you see certain blooms and you see the Amazon, you like, wow, that's bonkers. You come from that.
When you come from that, you don't exist just cavalierly. So I hope, I hope that those of y'all
who are listening here, I hope that you will really take a moment today and meditate on like,
where do I come from? Where do I come from? Where do I come from? And how do I keep going forward?
When I meditate, I meditate on the ocean. I meditate on the sea. And I say, bring me forward.
Bring me forward. Bring me forward. Bring me forward. Because that is always the goal. Bring
me forward. And I want you to know, I'm not crying right now because I'm sad. I'm furious. I am furious.
But you know what I'm furious about? I'm not even mad about them and talking to me. I'm furious
that we have allowed ourselves to be this corrupted. I am furious. I am furious that we have allowed
ourselves to be dismayed in such a way that we can't identify who our allies are. I'm furious.
I'm furious. Livid. I vexed. The oil, you can just run your boatswain. You can't even see the forest
with the trees. You can't see the sun with a shirt into your face. And that is who I am. And I know who
I am. And it is, it is so disheartening to me that we have allowed ourselves to be this taken off the
path that we can't even see who is and who is what. I'm furious. And no, I will not be brought into
their misery because I am joyful. I am so joyous. I am joy. This is my artwork. Joy. Oh, joy, purity of
heart. I am a pure heart. And so many people don't even know what that looks like because we live
in a processed world. We don't even know what purity is. We don't even know what that is,
but it exists. It is real. And some of us exist in that. Many of you do. Many of you here,
you have a pure heart. You have a pure soul. So there's a part of me that wants to say,
fuck you niggas, but I'm growing. I'm growing. So I just wanted to come on here and I wanted to pray
with y'all and I wanted y'all to, to be with me in this moment of turning shadow to light
because that is really the alchemy is turning shadow to light. And all day, every day we are
met with shadows. And our challenge is how do we turn it to light? And I know some people don't like
the term witch, or you don't like the term, you know, uh, conjurer, you don't like these terms,
but ultimately no matter what you're using, whether it is, you know, religion, whether it is
spirituality, no matter what you're using, that is the dance that we are doing. We are turning
shadow to light. That is what we are doing every single day is trying to consistently turn shadow
to light. That's it. That's it. We're trying to turn shadow to light. And so the video that I posted
before, that was the shadow. And I came on here to turn to light. And I really, um, I really am. I
appreciate all of you all. Again, I will be on tour. Come see me on tour. I am on Patreon. Follow
my Patreon. If you really want to support, because what I have also done in turning shadow to light is
I have left these shadow filled spaces. I have left these shadow filled spaces. I am $10,000 a month
away from page on Patreon from being able to no longer have to exist in Hollywood at all,
at all, and be able to just make content that turns shadow to light and to be able to donate money on a
regular basis, to be able to take care of my mother and to take care of my animals and to take care of
myself. Shadow to light. So thank you to everybody who has made that possible. Thank you to everybody
has shown me love. Thank you to everybody who has even just taken time to make a video in my support
because people like me, we need that. We need the words. We exist in language, not just action. We
exist in both. And that's why when people say things like, Oh, don't listen to the words. Just
this look at the actions. No, some of us need both because some of us exist in both because we know
that people exist in both. We have kinetic learners and we have auditory learners. We have people that
receive in multiple ways. And so we end up having to give double because I can't just give you the
action. I got to give you the linguistics and then they have to match and line up. Do you know how
much that is to exist? Do you know how much that is to expel? I expel that every single day in love
because that's what I was sent here to do. And I thank y'all so much for receiving that, for receiving
that and pouring that into me. And so when you take time to do that as well in a space that is trying
to diminish me, it means so fucking much to me. Thank you, Real J. Blessing. Thank you. So I just
want y'all to know everybody who's on here, whoever got something to say about me, I am fully available
to have something said to. Fully available. I'm actually in the process of creating a project
called Clear the Air where anyone who has had an interaction with me where they feel like they
weren't seen, we can get on and talk about it and clear the air because we need conflict resolution.
We need to be able to interact. We need to be able to evolve. We need to be able to redeem.
We need to be able to see each other without the process lenses in front of us. And I am dedicated
to that in my entire life. Like that is what I am dedicated to with all of the truth that is being
spoken about not just myself, but about politics, about all of this. We are behind a lens that is
shrouded in falsehood. Anyways, thank you. Last night I went and saw Don't Tell Mom,
The Babysitter's Dead, that my very, very good friend, Wade Elaine Marcus directed. This was a
beautiful movie, a beautiful cast of black actors and actresses that really just did the goddamn
thing. They are all so gifted and talented. These young people are going to shine and they're going
to expand. And I just want to send love out to them. And I want to shout out BET Plus for giving
space for that because that is what they should be doing. So I want to just say that while I'm here
and while I have you, but I am, I'm going to go punch my punching bag, but I really thank you all
for listening and shadow to light. That is your assignment for, that is all of our assignments.
That is our assignment. Shadow to light.